<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<cheatsheet title="Creating an RCP Application">

	<intro 
		href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
		<description>
            This cheatsheet will automatically launch wizards, 
            perform actions, and guide you through the individual 
            steps to create a Rich Client Application (RCP Application). 
            To learn more about using cheatsheets or to see a list of available cheatsheets 
            click help (?). To start working on this cheatsheet, 
            click the &quot;Click to Begin&quot; button below.
		</description>
	</intro>

	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.pde.doc.user/guide/rcp_project.htm" 
		dialog="true"
		title="Creating a New Plug-in Project">
		<action
			pluginId="org.eclipse.pde.ui"
		    param1="org.eclipse.rcp.mailApp"
            param2="org.eclipse.pde.ui.pluginContent.rcpmail"
			class="org.eclipse.pde.internal.ui.wizards.plugin.OpenProjectWizardAction"/>
		<description>
			To create an RCP application you must create a Plug-in Project.
			<br /><br />
			1. Select New -> Project... from the File menu and choose Plug-in Project
			from the list of wizards under the &quot;Plug-in Development&quot;
			category.
			<br /><br />
			2. Fill in the project name (eg. &quot;org.eclipse.rcp.mailApp&quot;). Click Next.
			<br /><br />
			3. Select &quot;Yes&quot; for creating a rich client application in the bottom section. Click Next.
			<br /><br />
			4. Select the &quot;RCP Mail Template&quot; from the list of RCP templates. Click Finish.
			<br /><br /><br />
			You may also use the "Click to Perform" button below to bring up the wizard.
		</description>
	</item>
    
	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.pde.doc.user/guide/product_configuration.htm"
		dialog="true"
		title="Defining a product configuration">
		<action 
			pluginId="org.eclipse.pde.ui"
			class="org.eclipse.pde.internal.ui.wizards.product.NewProductFileAction" />
		<description>
			The product configuration file allows you to configure, brand, and test your application.
			<br /><br />
			1. In order to create this file, select New -> Other... -> Product Configuration from the File menu.
			<br /><br />
			2. Type in a file name and select your RCP application from the list of existing products
			(&quot;org.eclipse.rcp.mailApp&quot;). The product file can be placed in any folder or  
			project. The file name must end with &quot;.product&quot;. Click Finish.
			<br /><br /><br />
			You may also use the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; button below to bring up the wizard.
		</description>
	</item>

	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.pde.doc.user/guide/pde_running.htm"
		title="Launching your product">
		<description>
			Once the configuration file has been created the product editor will
			open. On the overview page you can try launching the application
			by clicking the &quot;Launch the Product&quot; link.
		</description>
	</item>

	<item
		href="/org.eclipse.pde.doc.user/guide/product_export.htm"
		dialog="true"
		title="Exporting a Rich Client Application">
		<description>
			The product configuration editor also allows you to export RCP
			applications.
			<br /><br />
			1. Click the &quot;Eclipse Product export wizard&quot; link in the Exporting section 
			of the Overview page.
			<br /><br />
			2. In the wizard, enter a full path name to the archive. Click Finish.
			<br /><br /><br />
			When the operation completes, you will have an archive containing a ready to run copy of your
			application.
		</description>
	</item>
</cheatsheet>
