<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 

<!-- Composite Cheat Sheet -->

<compositeCheatsheet name="Create an RCP application using PDE">

   <!-- Task Group -->

   <taskGroup kind="set" name="Create an RCP application using PDE">
      <intro>
         This cheat sheet will guide you through the individual steps to 
         create a plug-in, define a plug-in based product, customize
         a product, export an RCP application and define a feature-based
         product using the Plug-in Development Environment (PDE).
         <br/>
         <br/>
         To assist you along the way, wizards and commands
         will be available for you to launch automatically.
      </intro>

      <!-- Task -->

      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Create a plug-in">
         <intro>
            This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to create a plug-in project
            for an RCP application and execute an RCP application plug-in using PDE. 
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="rcpapp/rcpapp-create.xml" />
         <onCompletion>
         	Congratulations!  You just created a plug-in for an RCP application!
         </onCompletion>
      </task>

      <!-- Task -->

      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Define a plug-in based product">
         <intro>
            This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to define a plug-in
            based product configuration for an RCP application and execute 
            an RCP application product using PDE.  
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="rcpapp/rcpapp-plugin-product.xml" />
         <onCompletion>
         	Congratulations!  You just defined a plug-in based product configuration for an RCP application!
         </onCompletion>
      </task>

      <!-- Task -->

      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Customize a product">
         <intro>
         This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to add window images,
         add a splash screen and customize a launcher for an RCP
         application using PDE.  
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="rcpapp/rcpapp-customize.xml" />
         <onCompletion>
         	Congratulations!  You just customized a product configuration for an RCP application!
         </onCompletion>
      </task>

      <!-- Task -->

      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Export an RCP application">
         <intro>
         This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to modify a build 
         configuration for an RCP application and export a 
         RCP application product using PDE.
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="rcpapp/rcpapp-export.xml" />
         <onCompletion>
         	Congratulations!  You just exported an RCP application!
         </onCompletion>
      </task>

      <!-- Task -->

      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Define a feature-based product">
         <intro>
         This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to define a feature-based product
         configuration using a plug-in based one and create a feature for an RCP
         application using PDE. 
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="rcpapp/rcpapp-feature-product.xml" />
         <onCompletion>
         	Congratulations!  You just defined a feature-based product configuration for an RCP application!
         </onCompletion>
      </task>


   </taskGroup>


</compositeCheatsheet>
